Grisko Ramirez

6199 Canterbury Dr, Culver City, CA 90230 Phone: 310-493-0230

E-mail: peramig@gmail.com

Objectives

Diligent support specialist with strong knowledge of Hardware, Software and Network Administration with 4+ years' experience with medium connectivity service agency. Obtained highest grade in build spec (100%) and quality (98.3%). Seeking to further IT career by growing with your team of professionals.

Education

Bachelor of Technology in Thermoenergetic (July 1995) Achieved certification on ISO 9000/9001 (February 1997) Hardware and software Technician (July 1999) Network Administrator (March 2001)

Experience

General Manager and IT Technician (September 2011 – Present) PCCM3 INC

Recruiting; training and supervising staff; ensuring compliance; overseeing stock levels; ordering or buying supplies; promoting and marketing; making improvements, customer service. Installing, Troubleshooting POS systems, Networks, WIFI.

Personal assistant (November 2006 - February 2011)

Time and daily management; scheduling of meetings; driver; correspondence; computer office work, customer service.

Network Administrator (March 2001 – October 2006) COPEXTEL, SA

Performs upgrades; securing, installing and configuration of servers; logs analysis; problem solving.

Hardware and Software Technician (July 1999 – March 2001) COPEXTEL,SA

Implementing control rules; daily work report; fixing, backups, upgrading and troubleshooting PCs.

Skills

- Exceptional understanding of computer hardware, router, switch, operating systems and applications.
- Quick and accurate diagnosis of network problems. Terrific knowledge of software, backups and update rollouts.

▶ Page 2 | [Type your phone number]